<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
    <title>Lindsey Tulloch - Privacy Enhancing Technologies</title>
    <subtitle>Master of Mathematics, Privacy and Security Researcher, Software Developer</subtitle>
    <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://onyiny-ang.github.io/tags/privacy-enhancing-technologies/atom.xml"/>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://onyiny-ang.github.io/"/>
    <generator uri="https://www.getzola.org/">Zola</generator>
    <updated>2023-07-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>https://onyiny-ang.github.io/tags/privacy-enhancing-technologies/atom.xml</id>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Lox: Protecting the Social Graph in Bridge Distribution</title>
        <published>2023-07-11T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2023-07-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://onyiny-ang.github.io/publications/lox/"/>
        <id>https://onyiny-ang.github.io/publications/lox/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://onyiny-ang.github.io/publications/lox/">&lt;p&gt;Lox incorporates each of the features described in this section into a novel privacy-preserving scheme. Lox allows users to build trust over time. Upon reaching a predetermined trust level, users are able to invite a number of friends. When a user is invited by a trusted user, they join Lox at a lower trust level and inherit their inviter’s bridges and the number of blocking events they have witnessed. These features are encoded as attributes in a user’s Lox credential, which allows the user to remain anonymous through their interactions with the system.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Lox: Protecting the Social Graph in Bridge Distribution (MMath Thesis)</title>
        <published>2022-05-26T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2022-05-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://onyiny-ang.github.io/publications/thesis/"/>
        <id>https://onyiny-ang.github.io/publications/thesis/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://onyiny-ang.github.io/publications/thesis/">&lt;p&gt;Access to the open Internet, free from surveillance and censorship, is an important part of fulfilling the right to privacy. Despite this, in many regions of the world, censorship of the Internet is used to limit access to information, monitor the activity of Internet users and quash dissent. Where access to the Internet is heavily censored, anti-censorship proxies, or bridges, can offer a connection to journalists, dissidents and members of oppressed groups who seek access to the Internet beyond a censor&#x27;s area of influence. Bridges are an anti-censorship tool that can provide users inside censored regions with a link to the open Internet. Using bridges as an anti-censorship tool is fraught with risks for users inside the censored region who may face persecution if they are discovered using or requesting bridges. &lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>OUStralopithecus: Overt User Simulation for Censorship Circumvention</title>
        <published>2021-11-15T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2021-11-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://onyiny-ang.github.io/publications/oustral/"/>
        <id>https://onyiny-ang.github.io/publications/oustral/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://onyiny-ang.github.io/publications/oustral/">&lt;p&gt;In many parts of the world, censors are continuously increasing their capacity to fingerprint, identify, and block censorship resistance tools&lt;br &#x2F;&gt; 
to maintain control over what can and can not be accessed over the Internet. In response, traffic replacement, which involves co-opting a steady &lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
stream of uncensored overt traffic to serve as a perfect cover for censored covert content, has been developed in an effort to provide undetectable &lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
access to the open Internet for those in censored regions. Despite the promise of this technique, creating a suitable stream of uncensored overt traffic &lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
that is high throughput, fingerprint and identification resistant, and does not overburden the user to generate, is an underexplored area that is critical &lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
to traffic replacement&#x27;s success. To address this, we propose OUStralopithecus (OUStral for short), a web-based Overt User Simulator (OUS) that browses the &lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
web as a human would in order to avoid being detected by a censor. We implement OUStral as a Python library that can be added to an existing traffic-replacement &lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
system. To evaluate OUStral we connect it to an existing traffic replacement system, Slitheen, that replaces media data such as images. Additionally, we&lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
implement WebM video replacement for Slitheen to demonstrate the high throughput that OUStral is able to provide. We show that OUStral evades being detected &lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
as a bot by state-of-the-art bot detection software while providing a high-throughput overt data channel for covert data replacement.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
</feed>
