<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
    <title>Lindsey Tulloch - User Simulation</title>
    <subtitle>Master of Mathematics, Privacy and Security Researcher, Software Developer</subtitle>
    <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://onyiny-ang.github.io/tags/user-simulation/atom.xml"/>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://onyiny-ang.github.io/"/>
    <generator uri="https://www.getzola.org/">Zola</generator>
    <updated>2021-11-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>https://onyiny-ang.github.io/tags/user-simulation/atom.xml</id>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>OUStralopithecus: Overt User Simulation for Censorship Circumvention</title>
        <published>2021-11-15T00:00:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2021-11-15T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              Unknown
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://onyiny-ang.github.io/publications/oustral/"/>
        <id>https://onyiny-ang.github.io/publications/oustral/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://onyiny-ang.github.io/publications/oustral/">&lt;p&gt;In many parts of the world, censors are continuously increasing their capacity to fingerprint, identify, and block censorship resistance tools&lt;br &#x2F;&gt; 
to maintain control over what can and can not be accessed over the Internet. In response, traffic replacement, which involves co-opting a steady &lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
stream of uncensored overt traffic to serve as a perfect cover for censored covert content, has been developed in an effort to provide undetectable &lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
access to the open Internet for those in censored regions. Despite the promise of this technique, creating a suitable stream of uncensored overt traffic &lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
that is high throughput, fingerprint and identification resistant, and does not overburden the user to generate, is an underexplored area that is critical &lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
to traffic replacement&#x27;s success. To address this, we propose OUStralopithecus (OUStral for short), a web-based Overt User Simulator (OUS) that browses the &lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
web as a human would in order to avoid being detected by a censor. We implement OUStral as a Python library that can be added to an existing traffic-replacement &lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
system. To evaluate OUStral we connect it to an existing traffic replacement system, Slitheen, that replaces media data such as images. Additionally, we&lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
implement WebM video replacement for Slitheen to demonstrate the high throughput that OUStral is able to provide. We show that OUStral evades being detected &lt;br &#x2F;&gt;
as a bot by state-of-the-art bot detection software while providing a high-throughput overt data channel for covert data replacement.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
</feed>
